<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="privacy">
\n
“Ouibot” Mobile Service Terms and Conditions \n\n

Article 1 (Purpose) \n
The Ouibot mobile Service Terms and Conditions ("Terms and Conditions" hereafter) is aimed to define the process, conditions and others with regards to Ouibot Service ("the Service" hereafter) provided by Joeun Safe Co., Ltd. ("the Comapny" hereafter). \n\n

Article 2 (Definitions of Terms) \n
Terms are defines as follows ; \n
	•	"The service" means that users purchase Ouibot device, install Ouibot App into the each user<![CDATA["'"]]>s smart device and thereafter use <![CDATA["'"]]>video calls, message sending/receiving and CCTV monitoring as such<![CDATA["'"]]>. \n
	•	Ouibot App ("the App" hereafter) means the mobile application installed into the smart device to use the Service (including video calls, message sending/receiving and CCTV monitoring as such) \n
	•	Users mean someone one who uses the service according to the Terms and conditions. \n\n

Article 3 (Validity of Terms and Conditions) \n
	•	The company should list the Terms and conditions on the website (www.oui-bot.com) so as to let members and users to be accessible to the Terms and Conditions. \n
	•	The company is entitled to change the Terms and Conditions unless it violates any laws and regulations. In this case, the company should notify the change 15 days before execution. \n
	•	Agreeing upon the Terms and conditions means that users are required to visit the website on a regular basis. The company has no obligation to notify each user(member) about the change of Terms and Conditions. \n
	•	Terms and Conditions become valid when users purchase the Ouibot device and agree upon the Terms and Conditions on mobile page, internet page or paper documents. \n\n

Article 4 (Protection of personal information) \n
	•	The Company should put efforts to protect personal information, while fulfilling its obligation any relevant laws. \n
	•	However, the company is exempted from its obligation aforementioned when personal information is leaked owing to users<![CDATA["'"]]> responsibilities. \n
	•	The company should not provide anyone (or any 3rd party) with personal information except circumstances as follows ; \n
	•	when laws and regulations allow \n
	•	when identification is needed \n
	•	when laws and regulations enforce \n\n

Article 5 (Approval and Restrictions of the Service) \n
	•	The Company is required to provide the service to members and users upon request except technical issues occur \n
	•	Users and Members should fill in the Service application form, if required \n
	•	Users and Members should provide the company with ; Users<![CDATA["'"]]> name, Phone Number, E-mail address, Sex, Date of Birth \n\n

Article 6 (Duties of Users) \n
	•	Users must not breach or violate laws and regulations by utilizing the Service or must not utilize the Service for the purpose of breaching or violating laws and regulations. \n
	•	Users must not be involved in privacy infringement by utilizing the Service. \n
	•	Users must not install or place the Ouibot device in public space without authorization of the government or the private company. \n
	•	The company is not responsible for data restoration generated by the Service. \n
	•	Users must keep their SD card and any data with their duties. \n\n

Article 7 (Service Features) \n
The company provides users with the Service as follows ; \n
	•	Home CCTV : Real time monitoring for surveillance \n
	•	Intrusion detection and inactivity sensing : Setting up intrusion detection mode and inactivity sensing mode \n
	•	Recording Intrusion Video Clips : When intrusion detection mode is activated, Recording Clip is offered \n\n
Article 8 (Governing laws) \n
The Terms and Conditions is governed by laws and regulations of Korea Government.


    </string>
</resources>
